(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
雪花ラミィ 生誕3Dヒーローショー ホロレンジャー
Yukihana Lamy's Birthday 3D Hero Show: Holo Ranger
ラミィ！
Lamy!
悪の軍団 迫りくる
The army of evil is approaching
平和な街を 壊す奴ら
Those who destroy our peaceful town
負けない心 燃え上がれ
Burn up, O heart that never gives in
正義の刃 振り下ろせ
Swing down the blade of justice
ホロレンジャー！
Holo Ranger!
五つの力 合わせれば
When our five powers combine
無敵のヒーロー 誕生だ
An invincible hero is born
雪花ラミィ！
Lamy Yukihana!
世界を救う 守護神
The guardian deity who saves the world
ホロレンジャー！
Holo Ranger!
迫るショッカー　地獄の軍団
Shocker is closing in, the legions of hell
原作　ホロレンジャー
Original: Holoranger
我らを狙う黒い影
A black shadow aiming for us
世界の平和を守るため
To protect the peace of the world
ゴーゴーレッツゴー　輝くマシン
Go Go Let's Go, the shining machine
ライダー（ジャンプ！）
Rider (Jump!)
ライダー（キック！）
Rider (Kick!)
仮面ライダー　仮面ライダー
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
ライダー　ライダー
Rider, Rider
ライダー（ジャンプ！）
Rider (Jump!)
ライダー（キック！）
Rider (Kick!)
仮面ライダー　仮面ライダー
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
ライダー　ライダー
Rider, Rider
第1話 ヒーロー爆誕！？雪花ラミィの旅立ち！
Episode 1: A Hero is Born!? Lamy Yukihana's Departure!
あっつ！
Hot!
いや火薬の量間違えて爆発させすぎちゃったよ。
Wow, I used the wrong amount of gunpowder and set off way too many explosions.
もうせっかくの眉毛が燃えちゃうよ。
Jeez, my precious eyebrows are gonna burn off.
あっ、ゆきみさん、ありがとう。
Oh, Yukimi-san, thank you.
おっ、みんな！今日は来てくれてありがとう。
Oh, everyone! Thank you for coming today.
そうです、今日はラミィの誕生日です。
That's right, today is Lamy's birthday.
そして、今年のラミィは一味違います。
And this year, Lamy is a little different.
今年も体力作りで力をつけてきたけど...
I've been building up my strength with physical training again this year...
みんな知ってる？なんでラミィがあんなに頑張ってたか。
Do you all know why Lamy was working so hard?
実はね、ヒーローになるためなんだ！
Actually, it's so I can become a hero!
ドドーン！
Ta-dah!
でも、ヒーローって言ってもいろんな形があるじゃん。
But even when you say "hero," there are many different types.
だから今日は自分だけのヒーロー像を探す旅に出ようと思うの。
So today, I'm going to set out on a journey to find my own ideal of what a hero is.
え、な、何だ？
Wh-What is this?
いや、やめろ！
No, stop it!
とりゃ！
Take that!
えい！
Hah!
ゆきみさん！
Yukimi-san!
ゆきみさん、ラミィを守ってくれたの？
Yukimi-san, you protected Lamy?
さっきもバイク片付けてくれたし。
You even cleared away the bike earlier.
ゆきみさんは本当にえらいなー。
Yukimi-san, you're really great.
よしよしよしよし。
There, there, there, there.
あ、だいふくもいたの？
Oh, Daifuku was here too?
ちょっとまた敵が来ないか見張っといて。
Keep a lookout in case more enemies show up.
今日はね、いろんなゲストを呼んでたくさんのかっこいいヒーローを見ることができるから、楽しみだね。
Today, we're inviting various guests so we can see lots of cool heroes, so I'm looking forward to it.
それじゃ、雪花ラミィ、ヒーロー探しの旅に行ってきまーす！
Well then, Lamy Yukihana is heading out on a journey to find a hero!
なんで...
Why...
なんでまたゆきみんばかり...
Why is it always just Yukimin...
僕だって...
Even I...
ガッチャマンの歌
Song of Gatchaman
The Song of Gatchaman
誰だ 誰だ 誰だ 空のかなたに踊る影
Who is it? Who is it? Who is it? A dancing shadow beyond the sky
白い翼の ガッチャマン
Gatchaman of the white wings
命をかけて 飛び出せば
If you risk your life and fly out
科学忍法 火の鳥だ
It's the Science Ninja Technique: Firebird
飛べ 飛べ 飛べ ガッチャマン
Fly, fly, fly, Gatchaman
行け 行け 行け ガッチャマン
Go, go, go, Gatchaman
地球は一つ 地球は一つ
The Earth is one, the Earth is one
おお ガッチャマン ガッチャマン
Oh, Gatchaman, Gatchaman
誰だ 誰だ 誰だ 海の地獄に潜む影
Who is it? Who is it? Who is it? A shadow lurking in the hell of the sea
強い勇気の ガッチャマン
Gatchaman of strong courage
嵐をさいて 雲きれば
Splitting the storm, cutting through the clouds
科学忍法 火の鳥だ
It's the Science Ninja Technique: Firebird
飛べ 飛べ 飛べ ガッチャマン
Fly, fly, fly, Gatchaman
行け 行け 行け ガッチャマン
Go, go, go, Gatchaman
地球は一つ 地球は一つ
The Earth is one, the Earth is one
おお ガッチャマン ガッチャマン
Oh, Gatchaman, Gatchaman
誰だ 誰だ 誰だ ビルの谷間に忍ぶ影
Who is it? Who is it? Who is it? A shadow creeping in the valley of buildings
赤い血潮の ガッチャマン
Gatchaman of the red blood tide
夕日を浴びて 駆け出せば
Basking in the sunset, if you run out
科学忍法 火の鳥だ
It's the Science Ninja Technique: Firebird
飛べ 飛べ 飛べ ガッチャマン
Fly, fly, fly, Gatchaman
行け 行け 行け ガッチャマン
Go, go, go, Gatchaman
地球は一つ 地球は一つ
The Earth is one, the Earth is one
おお ガッチャマン ガッチャマン
Oh, Gatchaman, Gatchaman
キン肉マンGo Fight!
Kinnikuman Go Fight!
ハッ ハッ
Ha! Ha!
[Go! Go! Muscle!]
リングに 稲妻走り
Lightning runs through the ring
炎の 戦士をてらす
Illuminating the warrior of flames
飛び散れ キン肉ビーム
Fly out, Kinniku Beam
勝利に 向かって
Towards victory
私は (ドジで)
I am (clumsy but)
強い (つもり)
strong (so I think)
キン肉マン
Kinnikuman
走る (すべる)
Run (and slip)
見事に (ころぶ)
beautifully (fall down)
ああ 心に愛がなければ Uh~ Uh~ Uh~ Uh~
Ah, if there is no love in the heart...
スーパーヒーローじゃないのさ (Ha~)
You're not a superhero
キン肉マン Go Fight!
Kinnikuman Go Fight!
ハッ ハッ
Ha! Ha!
[Go! Go! Muscle!]
嵐の 必殺技で
With a storm-like special move
けちらす 超人レスラー
Scattering the superhuman wrestlers
マットに 真っ赤な薔薇が
A bright red rose on the mat
今夜も 咲くのさ
Will bloom again tonight
私は (ドジで)
I am (clumsy but)
強い (つもり)
strong (so I think)
キン肉マン
Kinnikuman
誰もが (誰も)
Everyone (No one)
待って (いない)
is waiting (not really)
ああ 果てない夢を追いかけ Uh~ Uh~ Uh~ Uh~
Ah, chasing an endless dream...
ああ 果てない夢を追いかけ
Ah, chasing an endless dream
(Uh~ Uh~ Uh~ Uh~)
スーパーヒーローになるのさ (Ha~)
I'll become a superhero (Ha~)
キン肉マン Go Fight!
Kinnikuman Go Fight!
私はドジで 強い（つもり）
I'm clumsy but strong (I think)
キン肉マン
Kinnikuman
走る（すべる） 見事に（ころぶ）
I run (slip), beautifully (fall)
ああ 心に愛がなければ
Ah, if there is no love in your heart
(Uh~ Uh~ Uh~ Uh~)
スーパーヒーローじゃないのさ (Ha~)
You're not a superhero (Ha~)
キン肉マン Go Fight!
Kinnikuman Go Fight!
微かなる夕陽
A Faint Sunset
聞こえないように
So no one hears
俯く体を
My head bowed low
誰か包んで…
Someone, embrace me...
壊れる前に
Before I break
弾き出し嘲笑い
Cast out, laughed at
瞳を射つ
Striking the eyes
闇への引き金
Triggering the darkness
踏み込む強さより
Rather than the strength to step in
抗う痛みなら
If it's the pain of resisting
誰より傍で
Beside you more than anyone
喰らう Conscience
Devouring Conscience
引き千切られたプライドが
Torn-away pride is
心に巻くブリザード
A blizzard winding through the heart
ねえ ここから出してって
Hey, can I scream
叫んでいいの？
To get out of here?
埋もれた声は低い空が
The low sky always saved
いつも救ってくれたね
My buried voice, didn't it?
砕かれた幻想の果て
At the end of shattered illusions
でもまだ終わらせない
But I won't let it end yet
My heart will doubt...?
悲しみ宿った
Flowing through petals
花びらに伝う
Where sadness dwells
涙が堕ちた
Tears fell
儚き結晶
Fleeting crystals
未来さえ試されて
Even the future is tested
篩にかけて
Sifted through
残った現実
And what remains is reality
寡黙に見つめ合う
Silently staring at each other
夕陽はこの鼓動
The sunset is this heartbeat
生かしてくれるだろう
It will keep us alive
惑う With the truth
Wandering with the truth
転んだ今日が纏わりつく
Today, having stumbled, clings to me
萎れた感情伏せて
Hiding withered emotions
ねえ 早く気づいてよって
Hey, can I scream
叫んでいいの？
For you to notice quickly?
傾いた視界に淀む
In a tilted field of vision
道は見分けられるか
Can you distinguish the stagnated path?
ゲームは始まったばかり
The game has only just begun
この世に潜む現在(いま)を
The 'now' hidden in this world
My heart will want...
いらない痛みなんてないんだと
Adding my honest self, saying there's
素直な自分足して
No such thing as unneeded pain
ねえ ここまで来たよって
Hey, can I praise myself
褒めてもいいの？
For coming this far?
埋もれた声は低い空が
The low sky always saved
いつも救ってくれたね
My buried voice, didn't it?
砕かれた幻想の果て
At the end of shattered illusions
でもまだ終わらせない
But I won't let it end yet
My heart will believe
GO FIGHT! マジマジマジレンジャー
GO FIGHT! Magi-Magi-Magiranger
信じてフューチャー
Believe in the future
OK! オーライ! 勇気をこの手に
OK! All right! Courage in our hands
旅立て!
Set out!
君が超えたいものは何?
What is it you want to overcome?
大空 逆風 昨日の自分
The vast sky, the headwind, your yesterday's self
立ち向かう時 揺れ動く
When you stand tall, it wavers
その胸に湧き出すパワー
The power welling up in your heart
グリーングランド ピンクストーム
Green Ground, Pink Storm
ブルースプラッシュ イエローサンダー
Blue Splash, Yellow Thunder
レッドファイヤー
Red Fire
冒険の始まりさ
It's the beginning of an adventure
GO FIGHT! マジマジマジレンジャー
GO FIGHT! Magi-Magi-Magiranger
限界チャレンジャー
The limit challenger
勇気という名の魔法を持ってる
Possessing the magic called courage
GO FIGHT! マジマジマジレンジャー
GO FIGHT! Magi-Magi-Magiranger
夢見てフューチャー
Dreaming of the future
OK! オーライ! 明日をこの手に
OK! All right! Tomorrow in our hands
魔法戦隊マジレンジャー
Magical Squad Magiranger
旅立て!
Set out!
君が守りたいものは何?
What is it you want to protect?
友情 プライド 見えない絆
Friendship, pride, invisible bonds
くじけそうな時 そばにいる
When you're about to give up, I'm by your side
笑顔に初めて気がつく
I notice your smile for the first time
タウロス フェアリー
Tauros, Fairy
マーメイド ガルーダ
Mermaid, Garuda
フェニックス
Phoenix
5つの手重ねたら
If we overlap our five hands
GO FIGHT! マジマジマジレンジャー
GO FIGHT! Magi-Magi-Magiranger
限界チャレンジャー
The limit challenger
勇気が勝利の道を示すから
Because courage will show the way to victory
GO FIGHT! マジマジマジレンジャー
GO FIGHT! Magi-Magi-Magiranger
信じてフューチャー
Believe in the future
OK! オーライ! この声よ届け
OK! All right! May this voice reach you
魔法戦隊マジレンジャー
Magical Squad Magiranger
旅立て!
Set out!
唸る大地 風は吹き抜け
The earth roars, the wind blows through
たゆたう水 走る雷 燃える火
Fluctuating water, racing thunder, burning fire
GO FIGHT! (マジマジ) マジマジマジレンジャー
GO FIGHT! (Magi-Magi) Magi-Magi-Magiranger
限界チャレンジャー
The limit challenger
勇気という名の魔法を持ってる
Possessing the magic called courage
GO FIGHT! マジマジマジレンジャー
GO FIGHT! Magi-Magi-Magiranger
夢見てフューチャー
Dreaming of the future
OK! オーライ! 明日をこの手に
OK! All right! Tomorrow in our hands
魔法戦隊マジレンジャー
Magical Squad Magiranger
GO FIGHT! マジマジマジレンジャー
GO FIGHT! Magi-Magi-Magiranger
信じてフューチャー
Believe in the future
OK! オーライ! 勇気をこの手に
OK! All right! Courage in our hands
魔法戦隊マジレンジャー
Magical Squad Magiranger
旅立て!
Set out!
第2話 仲間の力! 心が導くヒーローのカタチ!
Episode 2: The Power of Allies! The Form of a Hero Guided by the Heart!
ふぅー。たくさんのヒーローと出会えて力はついたけど...
Phew. I've met a lot of heroes and gained strength, but...
...なんだかイマイチピンとこないんだよな。
...something's just not clicking yet.
ラミィ。
Lamy.
悩んでる顔してどうしたの？
Why do you have such a worried look on your face?
あ、かなたん。
Ah, Kanatan.
そうなの。
Well...
ヒーローってどうあるべきか分からなくなっちゃって。
I've lost sight of what a hero should be.
力があるだけじゃダメなんだ。
Just having strength isn't enough.
大事なのは、その力をどう使うかだよ。
What matters is how you use that strength.
かなたん。
Kanatan...
握力だけじゃ、世界は変えられない。
You can't change the world with just grip strength.
人々の心を守るのもヒーローの大事な大事な仕事なんだから。
Protecting people's hearts is also a very, very important job for a hero.
そっか。
I see.
力で守れないものもあるよね。
There are things that strength alone can't protect.
さっ、
Well then,
だからヒーローにも強い心が必要なんだ。
that's why a hero needs a strong heart.
どんなにピンチになっても、
No matter how much of a pinch you're in,
乗り越えるたびにどんどん強くなる心が。
it's a heart that grows stronger every time you overcome it.
さあ、僕と一緒に歌って、強い心を掴み取ろう！
Now, sing with me and let's grasp that strong heart!
うん！
Okay!
プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア
Precure, Precure, Precure, Precure, Precure, Precure, Precure, Precure
DANZEN! ふたりはプリキュア
作詞：青木久美子 作曲：佐藤直樹
DANZEN! Futari wa Pretty Cure
Lyrics: Kumiko Aoki / Composition: Naoki Sato
プリティでキュアキュア ふたりは プリキュア！
Pretty and Cure-Cure, the two of us are Precure!
プリキュア！
Precure!
一難去って また一難 ぶっちゃけありえない！
One trouble after another, seriously unbelievable!
制服着てても ふたりは むちゃくちゃタフだし
Even in our uniforms, the two of us are incredibly tough.
お互いピンチを乗り越えるたび 強く 強く 近くなるね Yeah!
Every time we overcome a pinch together, we get stronger and closer! Yeah!
your best! my best! 生きてるんだから
your best! my best! Since we're alive,
失敗なんて メじゃない！
failures are nothing!
笑う門に福来たるでしょ！
Fortune comes to those who laugh, right?
ネガティブだって ブッ飛ばす～！
We'll blow away even negativity!
生命の花 咲かせて！ 思いっきり～
Make the flowers of life bloom! With all our might...
もっとバリバリ！！
...even more intensely!
プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア
Precure, Precure, Precure, Precure, Precure, Precure, Precure, Precure
プリティでキュアキュア ふたりは
Pretty and Cure-Cure, the two of us...
プリキュア！
...are Precure!
たまには放課後のほほんと おしゃべり Very time!
Sometimes, a relaxing chat after school, Very time!
ウワサは恋する乙女の ビタミン剤だもん
Rumors say we're vitamins for girls in love.
闇夜に浮かんだ虹のかけ橋
A rainbow bridge floating in the dark night.
ここに降りて（ここに降りて）奇跡☆
Come down here (come down here), a miracle!
your best! my best! 全力だから
your best! my best! With all our might,
友情 愛情 サイコー！
friendship and love are the best!
論より証拠の輝くえくぼ
Brighter than any proof, our shining dimples,
必殺技で ハートキュン！
finishing move: Heart Kyun!
瞳に☆ほしい映して 思いっきり～
Reflected in our eyes, wishing on a star, with all our might...
もっとキラキラ！！
...even more sparklier!
プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア
Precure, Precure, Precure, Precure, Precure, Precure, Precure, Precure
プリティでキュアキュア ふたりは
Pretty and Cure-Cure, the two of us...
プリキュア！
...are Precure!
プリキュア プリキュア
Precure, Precure
プリキュア Chu Chu プリキュア Sha ba da ba da
Precure Chu Chu Precure Sha-ba-da-ba-da
Chu Chu Ah
明日は明日の風吹く マジ意味わかんない
Tomorrow, tomorrow's wind will blow, seriously don't know what that means.
今しか出来ない宿題 ガンバらなくっちゃ！
Homework that can only be done now, gotta do our best!
真逆のキャラでも あい通じてる
Even with opposite personalities, we understand each other.
夢を生きる（夢を生きる）チカラ☆
The power to live our dreams!
your best! my best! 生きてるんだから
your best! my best! Since we're alive,
失敗なんて メじゃない！
failures are nothing!
笑う門に福来たるでしょ！
Fortune comes to those who laugh, right?
ネガティブだって ブッ飛ばす～！
We'll blow away even negativity!
生命の花 咲かせて！ 思いっきり～
Make the flowers of life bloom! With all our might...
もっとバリバリ！！
...even more intensely!
プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア
Precure, Precure, Precure, Precure, Precure, Precure, Precure, Precure
プリティでキュアキュア ふたりは
Pretty and Cure-Cure, the two of us...
プリキュア！
...are Precure!
プリキュア プリキュア
Precure, Precure
（Chu wa）
(Chu wa)
ありがとう、かなたん。
Thank you, Kanatan.
なんとなくヒーローって何かが掴めた気がするよ。
I feel like I've somehow grasped what a hero is.
よかった。
I'm glad.
きっとラミィなら素敵なヒーローになれるよ。
I'm sure you can become a wonderful hero, Lamy.
その人を思いやる気持ちを忘れずにね。
Don't forget that feeling of caring for others.
わかった。
I understand.
ラミィなりのヒーロー像、考えてみるよ。ありがとう！
I'll try to think about my own image of a hero. Thank you!
それじゃあ、
Well then,
さらばー！
Farewell!
あー、行っちゃった。
Ah, she's gone.
よし、この調子で次に行くぞー！
All right, let's keep going like this!
あ、ごめんね、だいふく。
Oh, sorry, Daifuku.
今、忙しいの。
I'm busy right now.
後で構ってあげるから。
I'll play with you later.
あぁ...
Ah...
なんで...
Why...
なんで僕だけ見てくれないんだ...
Why won't anyone look at me...
ダラッタッタラッタ ダラッタッタラッタ
Dara-da-da-da... Dara-da-da-da...
時には僕らを理想を語る非凡な才能旅人で
Sometimes we're extraordinary travelers who speak of ideals
またはキャピタリズムに屈する傀儡の癒し恋人で
Or submissive puppet lovers yielding to capitalism
または虚像が書かれたボードを掲げるデモの一員で
Or members of a protest holding boards with illusions
いわば貴方にとっての優しい法螺吹き歩くオオカミ少年だ
In other words, I'm just a kind-hearted lying boy to you
名声を
Fame
体裁を
Decency
人生そのものを潰し合おう
Let's crush our lives together
恨んで 恨んで
Resent me, resent me
恨んでもたまに悔やんで
Sometimes even regreting resenting me
描きたい存在に背中をそそられる
The existence I want to draw lures me in
燃やして 燃やして
Burn it, burn it
燃やしても手が震えて
Even as I burn it, my hands tremble
嘘をハッタリをどうぞ重ねて着込んだんだ
Please, keep layering on the lies and bluffs
分かって 分かって
Understand, understand
分かって僕の正義を
Understand my sense of justice
無能な怪物を教理で燃やした
Burned the incompetent monster with doctrine
妬んで 妬んで
Envy me, envy me
妬んでいるまま選んだ
I chose it while still envying
その程度のちゃちな正解はいらない
I don't need such a cheap right answer
ダラッタッタラッタ ダラッタッタラッタ
Dara-da-da-da... Dara-da-da-da...
時には僕らは希望を託す聖人じみた歌人で
Sometimes we're saint-like poets entrusted with hope
またはキャピタリズムを隠した見た目だけの置物で
Or just ornamental figures hiding capitalism
または全てに噛み付く振りした得意なエキストラで
Or clever extras pretending to bite at everything
やはり貴方にとっての優しい法螺吹き歩くオオカミ少年だろう
You probably still see me as a kind-hearted lying boy
現状の
The current
展望も
Outlook
変貌も何もかもが無価値なんだ
Transformation, everything is worthless
存在を
Existence
本能を
Instinct
人生そのものを潰し合おう
Let's crush our lives together
恨んで 恨んで
Resent me, resent me
恨んでもたまに悔やんで
Sometimes even regreting resenting me
描きたい存在に背中をそそられる
The existence I want to draw lures me in
燃やして 燃やして
Burn it, burn it
燃やしても手が震えて
Even as I burn it, my hands tremble
嘘をハッタリをどうぞ重ねて着込んだんだ
Please, keep layering on the lies and bluffs
分かって 分かって
Understand, understand
分かって僕の正義を
Understand my sense of justice
無能な怪物を教理で燃やした
Burned the incompetent monster with doctrine
妬んで 妬んで
Envy me, envy me
妬んでいるまま選んだ
I chose it while still envying
その程度のちゃちな正解はいらない
I don't need such a cheap right answer
ダラッタッタラッタ ダラッタッタラッタ
Dara-da-da-da... Dara-da-da-da...
時には僕らは思想を諭す英雄的な歌人で
Sometimes we're heroic poets who teach ideologies
つまり貴方にとってのカリスマ気取った極悪非道なペテン師だ
In short, I'm just a wicked charlatan acting charismatic to you
ねえ、生まれてから今日までの間 どれくらいのごはんで
Hey, since the day I was born, how many meals
わたしたちはできてるかな 毎日ありがとう
Have made us who we are? Thank you for every day
もし食卓から おいしいが消えてしまったら ああ、迷わずに
If deliciousness ever vanished from the table, ah, without hesitation
どこにいたって 何をしてたって 取り戻しにいこう
No matter where we are or what we're doing, let's go get it back
あれは記念日の記憶
That's the memory of an anniversary
何気ないあの味も
And that casual taste too
忘れたりしない
I'll never forget
ずーっと一緒だよって 伝えなくちゃ
I have to tell you we'll be together forever
守りたいこの味は キミと笑いあう毎日の
The taste I want to protect is from our days of laughing together
いちばん傍で照らす あたたかい道しるべなんだ
The warmest guide, shining closest to us
みんなと 今を熱くするオモイ 育んでこれからも
Nurturing the feelings that heat up the present with everyone, from now on too
大切に刻もう キズナで結ぶスペシャリティ
Let's treasure every moment, a specialty bound by our bonds
ホラ、キミに届く おいしいの中の たくさんのストーリー
Look, reaching out to you, so many stories within this deliciousness.
めぐりめぐって ここにあるって 奇跡みたいだよ
Going round and round, it's like a miracle that it's here.
約束 つなげたい今がある キミと分け合いたい 未来へと
A promise, there's a "now" I want to connect to a future I want to share with you.
くじけそうな時も 負けないココロで立ち向かう
Even when I feel like giving up, I'll face it with an undying spirit.
みんなの しあわせなエナジーが作る この日々がうれしいよ
Everyone's happy energy creates these days, and I'm so glad.
デリシャスにあつまれ！ パーティは続いていくね
Gather for something delicious! The party is going to continue.
世界中 今も それぞれのストーリー
All over the world, even now, everyone has their own story.
ひとりずつが できることを がんばってるから
Because each and every one of us is doing our best with what we can do.
かならず！ 守りたいこの味は キミと笑いあう毎日の
For sure! This flavor I want to protect is the daily warmth of laughing with you.
いちばん側で照らす あたたかい道しるべなんだ
It's the warm guidepost that shines right by your side.
みんなと 今胸を熱くする想い 育んでこれからも
Together, let's nurture these feelings that warm our hearts from now on too.
大切に刻もう キズナで結ぶスペシャリティ
Let's cherish every moment, this specialty bound by our bonds.
約束 つなげたい今がある キミと分け合いたい 未来へと
A promise, there's a "now" I want to connect to a future I want to share with you.
くじけそうな時も 負けないココロで立ち向かう
Even when I feel like giving up, I'll face it with an undying spirit.
みんなの しあわせなエナジーが作る この日々がうれしいよ
Everyone's happy energy creates these days, and I'm so glad.
デリシャスにあつまれ！ パーティは続いていくね
Gather for something delicious! The party is going to continue.
大切に刻もう キズナで結ぶスペシャリティ
Let's cherish every moment, this specialty bound by our bonds.
第３話 闇を超えて！ ねぽらぼ絆ビームで奇跡を起こせ！
Episode 3: Beyond the Darkness! Create a Miracle with the NePoLaBo Bond Beam!
やっぱりねぽらぼだねー！
As expected of NePoLaBo!
ねぽらぼ！ハイ！ ねぽらぼ！ハイ！
NePoLaBo! High! NePoLaBo! High!
だいふく、やっと来てくれたー！
Daifuku, you finally came!
許さない... 許さない！
I won't forgive you... I won't forgive you!
うわぁぁぁ！
Waaaaah!
だ、だいふく...？
D-Daifuku...?
やみふく
Yami-fuku
まさか、あれは...
No way, could that be...
ラミィにかまってもらえず、負の感情が爆発して...
Since Lamy didn't play with him, his negative emotions exploded...
闇落ちした、やみふく...！
He's fallen to the dark side, it's Yami-fuku...!
そんな... だいふく、元に戻って！
No... Daifuku, please come back to your senses!
うるさーい！
Shut up!
きゃぁぁ！
Kyaaa!
ラミィ！
Lamy!
こうなったら、力ずくでも元に戻してあげる！
If that's how it's going to be, I'll bring you back by force!
元に戻って！
Return to normal!
うわぁぁぁ！
Waaaaah!
え、え、え？ やりすぎじゃないこれ？
W-wait, isn't this going a bit too far?
凄っ... 大丈夫？
Wow... is he okay?
ど、どうだ？
H-how's that?
ちくしょーー！
Damn it!
だいふく！
Daifuku!
あ、ラミィ待って！
Ah, Lamy, wait!
ちくしょーー！
Damn it!
きゃぁぁ！
Kyaaa!
ラミィーーーー！
Lamyyyyyy!
かまってー！
Play with me!
ヤミィ
Yami-Lamy
わぁー、ラミィちゃんが闇落ちさせられたー！
Oh no, Lamy-chan's been turned to the dark side!
これでラミィとずっと一緒だ...
Now I'll be with Lamy forever...
ラミィが相手でも止めるしかないよ！
Even if our opponent is Lamy, we have to stop her!
確かに、ラミィはタフだしね。まあ、ちょっとくらい痛くても平気でしょ。
True, Lamy is tough after all. Well, she'll be fine even if it hurts a little.
お、丁度いいところに。いくよ雪民、手を貸して。
Oh, perfect timing. Let's go Yukimi, lend us a hand.
雪民さん、いっけぇー！ そりゃあ！
Yukimi-san, goooo! Take this!
雪民ごめん！ あぁーー！
Sorry Yukimi! Aaaah!
いっけぇーー！
Goooooo!
かまって！
Play with me!
うわぁぁぁ！
Waaaaah!
ラーマーディーーー！
Laa-maa-diii!
ラーーマーーディーーー！
雪花ラミィ
Yukihana Lamy
えー、今度はラミィがデカくなっちゃったんだけど！
Wha—now Lamy's become huge!
仕方ない、あれを使おう。
It can't be helped, let's use that.
よし、みんな力を貸して！ラミィの良いところをたくさん言って、
Alright, everyone lend us your strength! Say lots of good things about Lamy,
祝福の鳥メカのパワーを溜めて攻撃だ！
charge up the Celebration Tori Mecha's power and attack!
ラミィ！
Lamy!
よしよしよし、いい感じ！よし、じゃあこのまま観客席のみんなも、
Good, good, good, that's it! Alright, everyone in the audience, keep it up,
ラミィの良いところめちゃ言ってって！
say lots of great things about Lamy!
で、うち等も言おう。
And we should say some too.
え？
Eh?
うち等も？
Us too?
言うの？
We're saying them?
あの、ラミィの良いところ言ってこ。
Let's say some good things about Lamy.
そしたら多分、ラミィも元に戻るから。いつもの感じね。
Then maybe Lamy will return to normal. Just like always, okay?
よし、レッツゴー！
Alright, let's go!
行くか！
Here we go!
ラミィちゃんに言いたいことがある！
Lamy-chan, there's something I want to tell you!
なーにー！
Wha-at!
ぜんぜんくだらないLINE秒で返事してくれて、
Thank you for replying to my totally silly LINE messages
ありがとう！
within seconds!
え、優しい！
Oh, how kind!
あら、いいじゃない。
My, that's nice.
いいじゃん、これいい感じじゃない？
Isn't it? This feels like it's working!
初
Celebration
あ、パワー溜まってきた溜まってきた溜まった！
Oh, the power is charging, it's charging, it's charged!
お、いい感じ！じゃあ次、おまる行け！
Oh, it's working! Alright, next, Polka, go!
ラミィに言いたいことがあります！
Lamy, there's something I want to tell you!
なーにー！
Wha-at!
いつもさ、こんな頼りないうち等のことまとめてくれたり、
You always manage us unreliable people,
突っ込んでくれたりして、本当に感謝してるんだ！
and play the straight man, I'm really grateful!
だからラミィ、お願い、元の姿に戻って！
So Lamy, please, return to your normal self!
いいんじゃない？
Isn't that great?
あ、溜まった溜まった！次！ししろん、ししろん行け！
Oh, it's charged, it's charged! Next! Botan, Botan, go!
ラミィちゃんに言いたいことがある！
Lamy-chan, there's something I want to tell you!
なーにー！
Wha-at!
いつも、ししろんが小ボケをいっぱいすると、
Whenever Botan makes lots of silly jokes,
全部に突っ込んでくれて、ありがとう！
thank you for reacting to all of them!
初
Celebration
来い、めちゃいい、いいじゃん！
Come on, this is great, isn't it!
ありがとう！あ！もっともっともっともっと！
Thank you! Ah! More, more, more, more!
ねね行け！ねね行け！二回目！二回目！
Nene, go! Nene, go! Round two! Round two!
そう、二周二周！
Yeah, second round!
ラミィちゃんに言いたいことがある！
Lamy-chan, there's something I want to tell you!
なーにー！
Wha-at!
秒で返事してくれるけど、
You reply within seconds,
スタンプで秒で終わらせようとするの、やめてね！
but stop trying to end the chat immediately with a stamp!
これ下がるんじゃね？大丈夫か？
Isn't this going to lower it? Is that okay?
上がるはずだ溜まった溜まった！
It should go up, it charged, it charged!
ほら、おまる行け！おまる行け！行け！
Look, Polka, go! Polka, go! Go!
ラミィに言いたいことがある！
Lamy, there's something I want to tell you!
なーにー！
Wha-at!
これをきっかけに、初期ラミィからやり直してみるのはどうでしょうか！
With this as a chance, why not try starting over from your debut persona!
バカお前！
You idiot!
やめろ！やめろよ！
Stop! Stop that!
初
Celebration
ほら、ダメだって！めちゃ下がってるって！めちゃ下がってる！
See, I told you! It's going way down! It's crashing!
ししろん、決めろ！決めろ！決めろ！
Botan, decide it! Finish it! End it!
ラミィちゃんに言いたいことがある！
Lamy-chan, there's something I want to tell you!
なーにー！
Wha-at!
いつもねぽらぼを大切にしてくれて、ありがとう！
Thank you for always taking good care of NePolabo!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
お、溜まった！溜まった溜まった！
Oh, it's charged! It's fully charged!
祝福
Celebration
これはいけるんじゃないか？やってくれるんじゃないでしょうか！
Isn't this it? I think this'll do it!
え、これは？
Eh, what's this?
あ、でもこれはパワーが溜まったんじゃないか！
Ah, but isn't this the power fully charged!
よしよし、ラミィ、元に戻ってくれ！
Alright, Lamy, please return to normal!
行け！ねぽらぼ絆ビーム！
Go! NePolabo Kizuna Beam!
だーいーふーくー...
Dai-fu-ku...
もーどーれー、ラミィーー！
Return, Lamy...!
ラミィ！ラミィ！
Lamy! Lamy!
うう、うう...
Ugh, ugh...
ラミィ、一体、元に戻った！
Lamy's... she's back to normal!
良かった！
Thank goodness!
大福の力で闇落ちしてたんだよ！
She'd fallen into darkness because of Daifuku's power!
いやでも正直、普段のラミィと全然変わらなかったから、うん。
But honestly, she didn't seem any different from her usual self, yeah.
元に戻って良かった。
I'm just glad she's back.
良かったー。
So glad.
あ！
Ah!
あれ？
Eh?
大福！
Daifuku!
お、大福...
Oh, Daifuku...
ごめんなさい。ちゃんと見てあげられなくて。
I'm sorry. I didn't take good care of you.
あ、ラミィ...
Ah, Lamy...
他人を思いやる気持ちが大事って教わったばかりなのに、
I was just taught that being considerate of others is important,
うまくできなくて、ごめんね。
but I couldn't do it well, I'm sorry.
やっぱりラミィには、大福や雪民さんがいないとダメなの。
In the end, I'm nothing without Daifuku and my Yukimin.
ラミィ！
Lamy!
大福、ずっとずっと一緒だよ。
Daifuku, we'll be together forever and ever.
ホロレンジャー
HoloRanger
完
The End
イェーイ！
Yeah!
はい、ということで、みんなラミィの生誕祭どうだったでしょうか？
So, everyone, how did you like Lamy's birthday festival?
面白かったー！最高だった！
It was fun! It was the best!
ラミィ誕生日おめでとう！おめでとうー！
Happy birthday, Lamy! Congratulations!
えー、ということでね、まだ終わりませんよ！
Well, it's not over yet!
重大告知が、2つあります！
I have two major announcements!
まずは、こちら！ドン！
First, this! Ta-da!
雪花ラミィ誕生日記念2025グッズ！
Yukihana Lamy Birthday Celebration 2025 Goods!
ということで、詳しく紹介していきたいと思います。
So, I'd like to introduce them in detail.
まずは、こちら！ドン！
First, this! Ta-da!
アクリル...アクリル...アクリルスタンド！
Acry... Acry... Acrylic stand!
テーマはですね、この後紹介いたしますフード付きタオルを身につけたラミィの元気な姿となっております。
The theme is Lamy looking energetic in the hooded towel that I'll introduce later.
みんな飾ってね！
Everyone, please display it!
続いては、こちら、ドン！おそろいトレーナー！
Next, this! Ta-da! Matching sweatshirt!
これはですね、サイバー衣装のトレーナーとおそろいのデザインとなっております。
This has the same design as the sweatshirt from the cyber outfit.
みんなラミィとおそろいにして着てね。
Everyone, please wear it to match Lamy.
続いては、こちら、ドン！ぬいぐるみキーホルダー ファンタジー私服衣装ver.ということで。
Next, this! Ta-da! A plush keychain of the Fantasy Casual Outfit version.
ユニーリアのね、あの夏衣装を身にまとったラミィのぬいぐるみキーホルダーとなっております。
It's a plush keychain of Lamy wearing that summer outfit from Unirya.
これをね、身につけていろんなところ、ラミィと一緒に、お出かけしてください。
Please wear this and go out to various places together with Lamy.
そして、続いては、こちら！雪民フード付きタオルとなっております！
And next, this! It's the Yukimin hooded towel!
これね、あの雪民さんの顔がフードになっているタオルね。イベント、あそこに居るけど会話してるわ。
This is a towel where the Yukimin's face is the hood. Oh, they're over there talking.
今後ね、イベントとかあった時に、こういうのを身につけてアピールしてくれると嬉しいです。
I'd be happy if you wear this to show your support at future events.
そして、フルセット購入特典はこちら！ドン！雪花ラミィ箔押し複製サイン＆メッセージ入り、描き下ろしポストカードとなっております！
And the full set purchase bonus is this! Ta-da! A newly drawn postcard with a foil-stamped replica signature and message!
ということで、以上、雪花ラミィ誕生日記念2025グッズでした！
So, that's it for the Yukihana Lamy Birthday Celebration 2025 Goods!
そして、告知2つ目！こちらは、新曲となっております！
And, the second announcement! This one is a new song!
この配信のあと、21時から、フルアニメーションMVが公開されます！
After this stream, at 21:00, the full animation MV will be released!
初めての、フルアニメーションMVとなっております。
It's my very first full animation MV.
各種音楽サイトのリリースはこのあと0時から配信されますのでよろしくお願いします！
It will be available on various music sites starting from midnight tonight, so please check it out!
ということで、みんな今日はたくさんたくさん、ありがとう！
So, thank you all so, so much for today!
おめでとう！ありがとうねー！バイバーイ！
Congratulations! Thank you! Bye-bye!
バイバーイ、ありがとう！こっち、こっちやで、こっち。大好き、雪花ラミィ。
Bye-bye, thank you! Over here, this way, this way. We love you, Yukihana Lamy!
ということで、最後に新曲聞いていってください。
So, please listen to my new song at the end.
それでは聞いてください。「無敵☆本気にサバイバー！」
Now, please listen. 'Muteki☆Honki de Survivor!'
ギリギリの綱渡り
Tightrope walking on the edge
弱音はポケットの奥
Hide your weakness deep in your pocket
しまい込んだら ただ進むだけ
Once tucked away, just keep moving forward
こけたって 即リスタート
Even if you fall, restart immediately
そこからがスタートライン
From there, it's the starting line
もう止まらないよ
I won't stop anymore
迷いなんて もう No No
No more hesitation, No No
不器用でも 前へ
Even if clumsy, move forward
しぼげてるヒマはなし
No time to be withered
ハイテンションで行こうじゃん
Let's go with high tension!
無敵☆本気だサバイバー！
Invincible serious survivor!
ゼロからでも何度だって
No matter how many times from zero
メンタル最強モードです 見ててね★
My mental is in the strongest mode, keep watching!
限界歓迎チャレンジャー！
Challenger who welcomes limits!
そう不安なんてさ笑い飛ばそう
Let's laugh off those anxieties
最前線 君次第
Front line is up to you
さあいくよ Ready Go ついてきてよね☆
Here we go, ready go, come along with me!
トラブルさえ追い風
Even trouble is a tailwind
ピンチもドキドキのスパイス
A pinch is also an exciting spice
Bring it on!! 胸を張れ
Bring it on!! Stand tall
遠回りも Go Go
Even detours are Go Go
転んでも Try だ！
Even if you fall, it's a try!
自分史上 一番へ
To my personal best ever
アクセル全開 ノンストップ！
Full throttle, non-stop!
無敵☆本気だサバイバー！
Invincible serious survivor!
ブレーキなんてお飾りでしょ？
Brakes are just for show, right?
ハート高鳴りモードです 感じて☆
My heart is in a throbbing mode, feel it!
完全燃焼フィニッシャー！
Complete combustion finisher!
誰より強く 夢を叫ぼう
Let's shout our dreams louder than anyone else
最終章 君次第
Final chapter is up to you
さあ行こう Ready Go 置いてかないから☆
Let's go, ready go, I won't leave you behind!
最強☆最愛チームメイツ！
Strongest, most beloved teammates!
君の声がパワーソース
Your voice is my power source
輝いて 駆け抜けよう 未来へ Fly high!!
Let's shine and run through to the future, fly high!!
超ハイテンションで行こうじゃん！
Let's go with super high tension!
無敵☆本気だサバイバー！
Invincible serious survivor!
ゼロからでも何度だって
No matter how many times from zero
メンタル最強モードです 見ててね★
My mental is in the strongest mode, keep watching!
限界歓迎チャレンジャー！
Challenger who welcomes limits!
そう不安なんてさ笑い飛ばそう
Let's laugh off those anxieties
最前線 君次第
Front line is up to you
さあいくよ Ready Go もっともっとついてきてよね☆
Here we go, ready go, keep coming with me more and more!
みんな、今日のライブどうだったー？
Everyone, how was today's live?
ラミィヒーローになれたかな？
Did I become a Ramy Hero?
新曲も、今までのラミィにはないかっこいい曲だったでしょ？
The new song was cool and unlike anything Ramy has done before, right?
みんなの感想、今日のハッシュタグをつけていっぱい聞かせてね！
Let me hear all your thoughts using today's hashtag!
そして、この配信のあと21時から、新曲「無敵☆本気だサバイバー！」のフルアニメーションMVが公開されます！
And, after this stream at 9 PM, the full animation MV for the new song "Muteki Honki da Survivor!" will be released!
ついにやってきました、フルアニメーション！
It's finally here, full animation!
今回のMVには、ラミィの大好きなものがたくさん詰まっています。
This MV is packed with things that Ramy loves.
このライブのあと、直接MVに飛ぶようになっているので、みんなこのまま待っててね。
Since you'll be redirected straight to the MV after this live, everyone please stay tuned.
さて、まだもう少し時間があるから、MVをチラ見せしちゃいます。
Well, since there's still a little time, I'll give you a sneak peek of the MV.
どうぞ！
Here you go!
無敵☆本気だサバイバー！
Invincible serious survivor!
ゼロからでも何度だって
No matter how many times from zero
メンタル最強モードです 見ててね★
My mental is in the strongest mode, keep watching!
限界歓迎チャレンジャー！
Challenger who welcomes limits!
そう不安なんてさ笑い飛ばそう
Let's laugh off those anxieties
最前線 君次第
Front line is up to you
さあいくよ Ready Go ついてきてよね☆
Here we go, ready go, come along with me!
このあと ミュージックビデオ公開！
Music Video will be released after this!
ラプラス・ダークネス / 白銀ノエル / 宝鐘マリン
さくらみこ / 天音かなた / 尾丸ポルカ
La+ Darkness / Noel Shirogane / Marine Houshou
Miko Sakura / Kanata Amane / Polka Omaru
風真いろは / 大空スバル / 白上フブキ
姫森ルーナ / 常闇トワ / 獅白ぼたん
Iroha Kazama / Subaru Oozora / Fubuki Shirakami
Luna Himemori / Towa Tokoyami / Botan Shishiro
施海ころた / saku39 / Syamo.G-しゃもじ- 他
Korota Sekai / saku39 / Syamo.G-Shamoji- and others
Syamo.G-しゃもじ- / 藍沢 / 織田有栖 他
Syamo.G-Shamoji- / Aizawa / Arisu Oda and others
藍沢 / 宮三 / 笹原節子 / RIA 他
Aizawa / Miyami / Setsuko Sasahara / RIA and others
神嵜昭ヨシキ / 山内昭平 他
Yoshiki Kanzaki / Shohei Yamauchi and others
雪民 / COVER Corp. STAFF
Yukimin / COVER Corp. STAFF
ホロレンジャー
生誕3Dヒーローショー
Holorenger
Birthday 3D Hero Show